{
    "id": "a9232cc69da047898e3dc46b0ebc54fa",
    "title": "Quantifiers Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "There is …………………… noise.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too much",
                "too",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………….. dislikes fish.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "very much",
                "very",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You are …………………… kind.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too much",
                "too",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Today is ………………….. colder than yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "very much",
                "very",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "His latest book is …………………… interesting than his last one.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a lot more",
                "quite more"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Come ……………………… quickly as you can.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "as much"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She is …………………… nuisance.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a quite",
                "quite",
                "quite a"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I am …………………… afraid that I can’t help you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "very much",
                "much",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She was ………………… annoyed to find him in her room.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "very",
                "very much",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "It’s ………………… cold day.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "such a",
                "such",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}